{
    "subject": "resource/Tank_Girl_(film)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:1990s_action_films",
    "human_readable": "Tank Girl is a subject of the category '1990s action films'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8362460136413574,
            "question": "Are there any popular films from the 1990s that share similar themes with Tank Girl?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8227274417877197,
            "question": "How did Tank Girl's style and aesthetic contribute to the visual language of 1990s action films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7323762774467468,
            "question": "What societal trends of the 1990s might have influenced Tank Girl's storyline?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6739330887794495,
            "question": "What genre is Tank Girl categorized as?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6230085492134094,
            "question": "What are some common elements found in 1990s action films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5809757113456726,
            "question": "Besides action, what other genres might Tank Girl be associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5542818307876587,
            "question": "Who are some prominent actors or directors associated with 1990s action films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4621948003768921,
            "question": "What decade was Tank Girl released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2376236766576767,
            "question": "Has Tank Girl had any lasting impact on popular culture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21155095100402832,
            "question": "What was the critical reception of Tank Girl upon its release?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Tank Girl is a subject of the category '1990s action films'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7214_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Tank Girl had any lasting impact on popular culture?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7214_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What decade was Tank Girl released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7214_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some prominent actors or directors associated with 1990s action films?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7214_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7214_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7214_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7214_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7214_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7214_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7214_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7214_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7214_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7214_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7214_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the film \"Tank Girl,\" produced in the 1990s, and describe it as an action film with a big budget. This aligns with the query that categorizes \"Tank Girl\" as a '1990s action film.'"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because the film Tank Girl (1995) is actually a science fiction film, not an action film, as per the context information provided.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}